Guide to the Frederic Bancroft Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Frederic Bancroft Papers,
[ca. 1890]-1930.
Bancroft, Frederic, 1860-1945.
62 linear ft (16,000 items in 147 boxes & 3 flats).
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY.
4078818
History
Scope and Content
The main portion of the collection is made up of letters, documents, notes, manuscript and typescript articles and speeches, and scrapbooks and notebooks which are contained in 270 envelopes, folders, manuscript boxes, and bundles. Another 153 bundles, boxes, folders, and envelopes are devoted chiefly to clippings, tear sheets, pamphlets, and books and other printed matter. Proofs of the printing plates for one of Mr. Bancroft's works on Carl Schurz are preserved in eleven envelopes. Pictorial material includes two envelopes of photographs, one envelope of photostats, thirty-four photographs, and eighty-five framed photographs, many with manuscript letters by or relating to the subject of the photograph. The collection is rich in the papers and personal correspondence of Frederic Bancroft and includes notes and various other source materials for his books dealing largely with blacks, the South, the Civil War, Seward, Calhoun, and the life and work of Carl Schurz. Also, a wealth of material by and about Edgar Bancroft (1857-1925), Frederic's brother and U.S. ambassador to Japan.
Subjects
Schurz, Carl, 1829-1906.; Bancroft, Edgar Addison, 1857-1925.; Seward, William Henry, 1801-1872.; Calhoun, John C. (John Caldwell), 1782-1850.; United States--Foreign relations--Japan.; United States--History--Civil War, 1861-1865.; African Americans.; African Americans--History.; Photoprints.; Scrapbooks.
Acquisition
1945 M45 Bancroft, Frederic Bequest
Alternate Formats
Royal Cortissoz letters are on microfilm.
Bequest of Frederic Bancroft, 1945.
- Series I: Cataloged Correspondence
  - A, F.W., Supt. of reading room, Library of Congress (Box 1)
  - Abbott, Lyman (Box 1)
  - Abbott, Willis J., Democratic Press Bureau (Box 1)
  - Adams, Charles F. (Box 2)
  - Adams, C.K. (Box 3)
  - Adams, E.D. (Box 3)
  - A.L. Baker & Co. (Box 3)
  - A.N. Marquis & Co. (Box 3)
  - Adams, Elizabeth Ogden (Box 3)
  - Adams, George B. (Box 3)
  - Adams, Henry (Box 3)
  - Adams, Herbert B. (Box 3)
  - Adams, Mary Ogden (Box 3)
  - Addison, Clare G. (Box 3)
  - Agaki, Roy Hidemichi (Box 3)
  - Aiken, William A (Box 3)
  - Albree, John (Box 3)
  - Alden, A.M., Harper's Magazine (Box 3)
  - Aldis, Graham (Box 3)
  - Aleollius, F. (Box 3)
  - Alexander, Edward Porter (Box 4)
  - Alexander, Mary L. (Box 4)
  - Alexander, W.(Treas, Augusta Exchange & Board of Trade) (Box 4)
  - Allen, Martin D. (Box 4)
  - Allen, Walter (Box 4)
  - Allis, Frederick A. (Box 4)
  - Allison, James W. (Box 5)
  - Allison, William B. (U.S. Senator) (Box 5)
  - Allston, Col. C.P. (Box 5)
  - Alston, Colonel Motte (Box 5)
  - Alvez, R.H. (Box 5)
  - Alvord, Clarence W. (Box 5)
  - Ambler, Charles H. (Box 5)
  - Ames, A. (Box 5)
  - Ames, Herman V., Dean, University of Pennsylvania Graduate School (Box 5)
  - Anderson, Addie (Box 5)
  - Andrews, Charles Ames (Box 5)
  - Andrews, Charles M. (Box 5)
  - Andrews, Matthew Page (Box 5)
  - Anesaki, M. (Box 5)
  - Appleton, William W. (Box 5)
  - Arnold, J.W. (Box 5)
  - Arnold, Wade E. (Box 5)
  - Attwell, Ernest T. (Box 5)
  - Avery, Myrtilla (Box 5)
  - Avery, S.L. United States Gypsum Company (Box 5)
  - Babcock, Kendric C. (Box 5)
  - Babbott, Frank L (Box 5)
  - Babbott, Frank L. Jr (Box 5)
  - Babbott, Mate (Box 5)
  - Bachachmid, Emil H. (Box 5)
  - Bachscimid, Paul (Box 5)
  - Bachtell, N.B. (Box 5)
  - Bacon, Augustus Octavius (Box 5)
  - Bacot, Thomas W. (Box 5)
  - Baetjer, Dr. Frederick Henry (Box 5)
  - Baird, Henry Carey (Box 5)
  - Baisnee, J.A. (Box 5)
  - Baker, Elizabeth (Box 5)
  - Baker, Ray Stannard (Box 5)
  - Balch, Ernest A. (Box 5)
  - Baldwin, G.S. (Box 5)
  - Baldwin, George J. (Box 5)
  - Ball, Ivar H. (Box 5)
  - Ball, R. Ella (Box 5)
  - Ballagh, James C. (Box 5)
  - Bancroft, Edgar A. (Box 6-11)
  - Bancroft, Frederic (Box 12-30)
  - Bancroft, Francis (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, Edwin A (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, George (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, H.E. (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, Hubert Howe (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, Margaret (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, Marion V (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, Mary L. (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, Ralph L (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, Richard (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, Sarah (Box 31)
  - Barbee, David Rankin (Box 31)
  - Barbour, James (Box 31)
  - Barker, Edwin L. (Box 31)
  - Barker, Eugene C. (Box 31)
  - Barker, Wharton (Box 31)
  - Barlow, Ellen S. (Mrs Francis C.) (Box 31)
  - Barnes, Thurlow W. (Box 31)
  - Barney, Hiram (Box 31)
  - Barney, Sarah (Box 31)
  - Barnwell, Joseph W. (Box 31)
  - Barry, N.A. (Box 31)
  - Bassett, John S. (Box 31)
  - Bateman, Newton (Box 31)
  - Battle, Kemp P. (Box 31)
  - Bayard, Thomas F. (Box 31)
  - Beall, Mary Stevens (Box 31)
  - Beane, D. (Box 31)
  - Bear, R.G. (Box 31)
  - Beardley, William H. (Box 31)
  - Beattie, Mrs. William (Box 31)
  - Beaumarchais, D. de (Box 31)
  - Bebel, A. (Box 31)
  - Beck, James M. (Box 31)
  - Becker, Bertha V. (Box 31)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward (Box 31)
  - Beecher, William C. (Box 31)
  - Beer, William (Box 31)
  - Belden, J.J. (Rep) (Box 32)
  - Bell, Elsie Graham (Box 32)
  - Bell, Elsie May (Box 32)
  - Bell, Mabel Gardiner (Box 32)
  - Bell, Marian H. Graham (Box 32)
  - Bellows, Dr George E. (Box 32)
  - Bellows, Stella F. (Box 32)
  - Bennett, Malvina M. (Box 32)
  - Bowles, Samuel (Box 32)
  - Benton, Joel (Box 32)
  - Boyd, Allen R. (Box 32)
  - Bernheim, Abraham C. (Box 33)
  - Boyd, J.B. (Box 33)
  - Bernheim, Julius C. (Box 33)
  - Berton, Edmond D. (Box 33)
  - Bey, Raif (Box 33)
  - Beydon, Andre (Box 33)
  - Beydon, Eliane (Box 33)
  - Beydon, Flaurette (Box 33)
  - Beydon, Jacaueline (Box 33)
  - Beydon, Jean (Box 33)
  - Beydon, L. (Box 33)
  - Biddle, John M. (Box 34)
  - Bigelow, Ellett (Box 34)
  - Bigelow, H.E. (Box 34)
  - Bigelow, John (Box 34)
  - Bigelow, Mab (Box 34)
  - Bigelow, Mary R. (Box 34)
  - Bigelow, Mrs. H.R. (S.Z.) (Box 34)
  - Bigelow, Otis (Box 34)
  - Bigelow, Poultney (Box 34)
  - Bigelow, Sally (Box 34)
  - Bigelow, Sarah Z. (Box 34)
  - Bikle, Lucy L. Cable (Box 35)
  - Billings, J.S. (Box 35)
  - Bishop, George R. (Box 35)
  - Bishop, J.B. (Box 35)
  - Bissell, A.D. (Box 35)
  - Bitter, Karl T.F. (Box 35)
  - Blackford, L.M. (Box 35)
  - Blacklidge, Myrtle Tanner (Box 35)
  - Blackman, R.C. (Box 35)
  - Blaine, Anita (Box 35)
  - Blaine, Harriet S. (Box 35)
  - Blaine, James G. (Box 35)
  - Blaine, Walker (Box 35)
  - Blair, A.H. (Box 35)
  - Blair, David E. (Box 35)
  - Blair, Gist (Box 35)
  - Blair, M.W. (Box 35)
  - Blair, Max F. (Box 35)
  - Blanc, Madame Thomas (Box 35)
  - Blanc, Thomas (Box 35)
  - Blatchford, Larry A. (Box 35)
  - Blatchford, Paul (Box 35)
  - Blau, Max F. (Box 35)
  - Bogan, William J. (Box 35)
  - Boordman, W.J. (Box 35)
  - Boucher, C.S. (Box 35)
  - Bourne, Edward G. (Box 35)
  - Bousa, Marie (Box 35)
  - Bousignac, M. de (Box 35)
  - Boutwell, George S. (Box 35)
  - Bowdoin, J.G. (Box 35)
  - Bowen, Clarence W. (Box 35)
  - Bowen, J.W.E. (Box 35)
  - Bowerman, George F. (Box 35)
  - Bowie, G.C. (Box 35)
  - Bowker, R.R. (Box 35)
  - Boyd, William Kenneth (Box 35)
  - Boynton, Charles A. (Box 35)
  - Boynton, Delight (Box 35)
  - Brabson, Fay W. (Box 35)
  - Bracq, Jean Charlemagne (Box 35)
  - Bradley, A.G. (Box 35)
  - Bradley, Joseph L. (Box 35)
  - Bradley, Mary M. (Box 35)
  - Breels, K.B. (Box 35)
  - Brentano's (J.W.F.) (Box 35)
  - Brett, George P. (Box 35)
  - Brewer, Arthur H. (Box 35)
  - Bridgeforth, G.R. (Box 35)
  - Bridges, Harry W. (Box 35)
  - Bridges, Robert (Box 35)
  - Britt, Albert (Box 35)
  - Brockhaus, Herman H. (Box 35)
  - Brooks, Adele (Box 35)
  - Brown, J. Thompson (Box 35)
  - Brown, Mary Gratz (Box 35)
  - Brown, Samuel H. (Box 35)
  - Brown, Ward (Box 35)
  - Brown, William Garratt (Box 35)
  - Browne, William Hand (Box 35)
  - Bruce, Philip Alexander (Box 35)
  - Bryan, (Judge) George D. (Box 35)
  - Bryan, Geneva (Box 35)
  - Bryan, William J. (Box 35)
  - Budd, Britton I (Box 35)
  - Burgess, J.W. (Box 36)
  - Burnett, Charles (Box 36)
  - Burnett, Prances H.E. (Box 36)
  - Burr, Anna Robeson (Box 36)
  - Burrell, W.P. (Box 36)
  - Burrows, Julius C. (Box 36)
  - Burt, Lilian (Box 36)
  - Burt, Silas W. (Box 36)
  - Burton, Theodore E. (Box 36)
  - Burton, Theodore E. (Box 36)
  - Butler, Charles Henry (Box 36)
  - Butler, Edward B. (Box 36)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray (Box 36)
  - Butler, Pierce (Box 36)
  - Cable, Eva Stevenson (Box 36)
  - Cable, George W. (Box 36)
  - Cahoon, B.B. (Box 36)
  - Cailleau, Josephine (Box 36)
  - Calcott, W.H. (Box 36)
  - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo (Box 36)
  - Cambron, Rebecca (Box 36)
  - Cameron, Hamilton (Box 36)
  - Campbell, Elizabeth (Box 36)
  - Capers, S.D. (Box 36)
  - Carbarieu, Marie (Box 36)
  - Cardozo, F.L. (Box 36)
  - Carnegie, Andrew (Box 36)
  - Carpenter, Fred W. (Box 36)
  - Carr, Col Clark E. (Box 36)
  - Carrott, M.F. (Box 36)
  - Corning, Charles R. (Box 36)
  - Carson, Clayton W. (Box 36)
  - Carson, James Petigru (Box 36)
  - Carter, H.A.P. (Box 36)
  - Carter, Mr. & Mrs. [Henry Alpheus Peirce] (Box 36)
  - Cary, Edward (Box 36)
  - Catching, W.S. (Box 36)
  - Caterall. Helen Turinicliff (Mrs. Ralph) (Box 36)
  - Chadwick, F.E. (Box 36)
  - Chadwick, J.W. (Box 36)
  - Channing, Edward (Box 36)
  - Chalkley, Lyman (Box 36)
  - Chamberlain, Daniel H. (Box 36)
  - Chamberlain, Eugene Tyler (Box 36)
  - Chamberlain, Frank (Box 36)
  - Chambers, D.L. (Box 36)
  - Chambers, Josiah (Box 36)
  - Chandler, W. (Box 36)
  - Channing, Edward (Box 36)
  - Chaplan, H.W. (Box 36)
  - Chapman, John Jay (Box 36)
  - Chappell, Jay F. (Box 36)
  - Charles A. (Box 36)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons (Box 36)
  - Cheves, Langdon (Box 36)
  - Childs, Lillian L. (Box 36)
  - Chipman, J. Logan (Rep.) (Box 36)
  - Christie, S. (Box 36)
  - Clark, A. Howard (Box 36)
  - Clark, Charles C. (Box 36)
  - Clarke, Enos (Box 36)
  - Clarke, Helen Gaines (Box 36)
  - Clarke, Lucretia D. (Box 36)
  - Clay, Cassius Marcellus (Box 36)
  - Clendenin, M. (Box 36)
  - Clendenin, F.M. (Box 36)
  - Clendenin, Gabrielle Greeley (Box 36)
  - Cleveland, Frances F. (Box 36)
  - Cliabee, Azalea (Box 36)
  - Clover, Richardson (Box 36)
  - Coates, Joseph Honor (Box 37)
  - Cochran, W.C. (Box 37)
  - Codman, Charles R. (Box 37)
  - Colby, F.N. (Box 37)
  - Cole, Haydn S. (Box 37)
  - Coleman, Annah (Box 37)
  - Collins Winfield H. (Box 37)
  - Collins, C.P. (Box 37)
  - Colston, Frederick M. (Box 37)
  - Colton, Ellen M. (Box 37)
  - Colton, Emily M. (Box 37)
  - Colton, Margery (Box 37)
  - Colton, Mrs. David (Box 37)
  - Comstock, [Ada] (Box 37)
  - Conant, Ernest L (Box 37)
  - Conger, Harriet (Box 37)
  - Conger, J.L. (Box 37)
  - Connell, Thomas (Box 37)
  - Connvell, Mary E. (Box 37)
  - Conway, M.D. (Box 37)
  - Conway, P.V.D. (Box 37)
  - Cook, William C. (Box 37)
  - Coolidge, Archibald (Box 37)
  - Coombs, F.J. (Box 37)
  - Corbin, Henry C. (Box 37)
  - Corbin, Katherine (Box 37)
  - Corbin, R.W. (Box 37)
  - Cornee, Lillian M. (Box 37)
  - Corrigan,.J.W. (Box 37)
  - Cortissoz, Katharine (Box 37)
  - Cortissoz, Royal (Box 37)
  - Corwin, Edward J. (Box 37)
  - Coulet, Jules (Box 37)
  - Count Kabayama (Box 37)
  - Couper, B.K. (Box 37)
  - Cowley, Malcolm (Box 37)
  - Cox, I.J. (Box 37)
  - Cox, Kenyon (Box 37)
  - Cox, William R. (Box 37)
  - Craig, John A. (Box 37)
  - Crawley, Charles (Box 37)
  - Crittenden, S.S. (Box 37)
  - Croll, June (Box 37)
  - Crouse, Lola M. (Box 37)
  - Crouse, William L. (Box 37)
  - Crowell, J.C. (Box 37)
  - Cruce and Potter (Box 37)
  - Cumming, Joseph B. (Box 37)
  - Cummings, Amos J. (Box 37)
  - Cunningham, Austin (Box 37)
  - Curry, I.S.M. (Box 37)
  - Curtis, Charles (Box 37)
  - Curtis, Elizabeth Burrill (Box 37)
  - Curtis, F.S. (Box 37)
  - Curtis, George William (Box 37)
  - Curtis, John Pearsons (Box 37)
  - Curtis, William E. (Box 37)
  - Cushing J.P. (Box 37)
  - Dana, Richard H. (Box 38)
  - Daniels, N.L. (Box 38)
  - Darden, M.W. (Box 38)
  - Daves, Graham (Box 38)
  - Davidson, Carter (Box 38)
  - Davis, Alice (Box 38)
  - Davis, Charles Henry (Box 38)
  - Davis, Charles W. (Box 38)
  - Davis, J.C. Bancroft (Box 38)
  - Davis, Mrs. Jefferson (Box 38)
  - Davis, Mrs. Jefferson (Box 38)
  - Davis, O.K. (Box 38)
  - Dawson, John (Box 38)
  - Day, W.A. (Box 38)
  - Daytore, Anna L (Box 38)
  - de Geoffroy, Antoine (Box 38)
  - de Geofrey, George (Box 38)
  - De Leon, Thomas Cooper (Box 38)
  - de Martigue, V. (Box 38)
  - De Maulde, R. (Box 38)
  - De Russy, Rene A. (Box 38)
  - Deas, Anne S. (Box 38)
  - Decker, Clement (Box 38)
  - Dehron, J.C. (Box 38)
  - DeJonge, Alfred R.W. (Box 38)
  - Delcasse, Theophile (Box 38)
  - De Leon, J.C. (Box 38)
  - Dening, Horace E. (Box 38)
  - Dent, James T. (Box 38)
  - Derby, George (Box 38)
  - D'Erlanger, Mathilde S. (Box 38)
  - Des Garennes, Jean F.P. (Box 38)
  - DetwiHer, John K. (Box 38)
  - Dewey, Melvil (Box 38)
  - DeWitt, David M. (Box 38)
  - Dick, Robert (Box 38)
  - Dickinson, L.J. (Box 38)
  - Dickover, N.H. (Box 38)
  - Dickson, Frank S. (Box 38)
  - Dinsmore, Rev. Dr. (Box 38)
  - Dittus, R.W. (Box 38)
  - Dix, Morgan (Box 38)
  - Doar, Daniel David (Box 38)
  - Dodd, William E. (Box 39)
  - Dodge, Alice (Box 39)
  - Dodge, William W. (Box 39)
  - Douglas, Albert (Box 39)
  - Douglas, Lucey T. (Box 39)
  - Douglass, Frederick (Box 39)
  - Dow, Caroline B. (Box 39)
  - Drane, Robert Brent (Box 39)
  - Du Bois, William Edward Burghardt (Box 39)
  - Dudley, Lilian M. (Box 39)
  - Duffel, Henry L. (Box 39)
  - Dufour, Germain (Box 39)
  - Durgan, John A. (Box 39)
  - Duhme, Charlotte (Box 39)
  - Duncan-Clark, T.J. (Box 39)
  - Dunlop, Dr. John (Box 39)
  - Dunn, Elizabeth Boggs (Box 39)
  - Dunning, William A., 1887-1907 (Box 40)
  - Dunning, William A. (Box 41)
  - DuPont, Henry A. (Box 41)
  - Durson, C.B. (Box 41)
  - E., R. (Box 42)
  - Earner, Charles (Box 42)
  - Easum, Chester Verne (Box 42)
  - Eaton, G.D. (Box 42)
  - Edmunds, Mary M. (Box 42)
  - Edwards, John O. (Box 42)
  - Elliott, William (Box 42)
  - Ells-worth, N.M. (Box 42)
  - Elson, Henry W. (Box 42)
  - Emerson, Edward W. (Box 42)
  - Engert, A. Van Hemert (Box 42)
  - Engle, Edward (Box 42)
  - Enrich, Walter L. (Box 42)
  - Ereme, H.T. (Box 42)
  - Erickson, James F. (Box 42)
  - Erlanger (Box 42)
  - Estes, Frederick R. (Box 42)
  - Estes, Grace D.C. (Box 42)
  - Eustis, Allain (Box 42)
  - Evans, Bowie W. (Box 42)
  - Evarts, William Maxwell (Box 42)
  - Farwell, C.B. (Box 42)
  - Farnan, Henry W. (Box 42)
  - Farrand, Max (Box 42)
  - Farwell, John V. (Box 42)
  - Faust, A.B. (Box 42)
  - Faymonville, Philip R. (Box 42)
  - Fechteler, A.F. (Box 42)
  - Fendon, Howard W. (Box 42)
  - Ferris, Stella A. (Box 42)
  - Ficklen, Bessie A. (Box 42)
  - Field, E.S. (Box 42)
  - Fife, Robert Herndon (Box 42)
  - Filer, E. (Box 42)
  - Finley, Robert (Box 42)
  - Finley; John H. (Box 42)
  - Firth, C.H. (Box 42)
  - Firty, James Wallis (Box 42)
  - Fish, Hamilton (Box 42)
  - Fish, Hamilton, Jr. (Box 42)
  - Fisher, N. Smith (Box 42)
  - Fitch, Ashbel P. (Box 42)
  - Fitzpatrick, John C. (Box 42)
  - Flagg, Charles Noel (Box 42)
  - Fleisher, B.W. (Box 42)
  - Fleming, William H. (Box 42)
  - Flickinger, Otto (Box 42)
  - Flint, Grover (Box 42)
  - Foord, John (Box 43)
  - Foote, C. Eugene (Box 43)
  - Forbesy Archibald (Box 43)
  - Ford, Worthington C. (Box 43)
  - Forgan, James B. Jr. (Box 43)
  - Fortune, T. Thomas (Box 43)
  - Foster, Charles W. (Box 43)
  - Foster, Herbert D. (Box 43)
  - Fourcade, Leontine (Box 43)
  - Fouret, F. (Box 43)
  - Frances, Maude (Box 43)
  - Frank. C.S. (Box 43)
  - Free, F.O. (Box 43)
  - Freeman, Douglas Southall (Box 43)
  - French, Henry R. (Box 43)
  - French, John C. (Box 43)
  - French, S.G. (Box 43)
  - Freund, Ernst (Box 43)
  - Fuess, Claude Moore (Box 43)
  - Fulkerson, Jennie (Box 43)
  - Fuller, H. De W (Box 43)
  - Fuller, H.B. (Box 43)
  - Fulton, S.Q. (Box 43)
  - Funk, C.S. (Box 43)
  - Furst, Frederick V. (Box 43)
  - Furst, J.H. (Box 43)
  - Gabrielle Greeley (Box 43)
  - Gage, Eleanor Patton (Box 44)
  - Gale, George W. (Box 44)
  - Gardner, William (Box 44)
  - Garennes, Jean F.P. des (Box 44)
  - Garfield, James R. (Box 44)
  - Garland, A.H. (Box 44)
  - Garland, Hamlin (Box 44)
  - Garner, James W. (Box 44)
  - Garrison, Francis J. (Box 44)
  - Garrison, George P. (Box 44)
  - Garrison, Philip McK (Box 44)
  - Garrison, W.P. (Box 44)
  - Garrison, Wendell P. (Box 44)
  - Gaus, Sarah B. (Box 44)
  - Geisler, Selma (Box 44)
  - Gennung, John F. (Box 44)
  - Gericke, M.L. (Box 44)
  - Gifford, Walter S. (Box 44)
  - Gilbert, Charles E. (Box 44)
  - Gilbert, W.B. (Box 44)
  - Gilder, J.B. (Box 44)
  - Gilder, Jeanette L. (Box 44)
  - Gilder, Richard Watson (Box 44)
  - Gillentine, Flora M. (Box 44)
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit (Box 44)
  - Gilmer, E.L. (Box 44)
  - Gilmore, James R. (Box 44)
  - Gilpin, E. H. (Box 44)
  - Girnberger, M. Jr. (Box 44)
  - Gladstone, William Ewart (Box 44)
  - Godard, George S. (Box 44)
  - Godkin, Edwin Lawrence (Box 44)
  - Godkin, Katherine (Mrs. E.L.) (Box 44)
  - Godkin, Lawrence (Box 44)
  - Going, Charles Buxton (Box 44)
  - Goodwin, Elliot H. (Box 44)
  - Gore, James H. (Box 44)
  - Gorham, George C. (Box 44)
  - Gorham, Maude Bassett (Box 44)
  - Gorman, Arther Pue (Box 44)
  - Gorrell, Warren (Box 44)
  - Grace, Theodosia Martin (Box 45)
  - Graham, George G. (Box 45)
  - Graham, Hettie W. (Box 45)
  - Grant, Frederick Dent (Box 45)
  - Grant, H.B. (Box 45)
  - Grant, M.P. (Box 45)
  - Graves, William C. (Box 45)
  - Gray, George (Box 45)
  - Green, Bernard B. (Box 45)
  - Greene, Caroline B. (Box 45)
  - Greene, Dr Frederick W. (Box 45)
  - Greene, Evarts B. (Box 45)
  - Greene, Henry F. (Box 45)
  - Greene, Jerome D. (Box 45)
  - Greenfield, Kent Roberts (Box 45)
  - Greenrlet, Ferris (Box 45)
  - Gregory, Charles Noble (Box 45)
  - Grierson, S.W. (Box 45)
  - Griffith Coal Company (Box 45)
  - Grossmann, Gertrude Hubbard (Box 45)
  - Grosvenor, C.H. (Box 45)
  - Grosvenor, Edwin A. (Box 45)
  - Grosvenor, Ellen Sage (Box 45)
  - Grosvenor, Gilbert (Box 45)
  - Grosvenor, William. M. (Box 45)
  - Grow, Galusha A. (Box 45)
  - Guedalla, Rowena (Box 45)
  - Hackett, Chauncey (Box 46)
  - Hackett, Frank W. (Box 46)
  - Hadnott, W.W. (Box 46)
  - Haggard, Sewell (Box 46)
  - Hale, Edward Everett (Box 46)
  - Hale, Edward Everett, Jr. (Box 46)
  - Hale, Harry Clay (Box 46)
  - Hall, Wilmer L. (Box 46)
  - Halsey, A.L. (Box 46)
  - Halstead, Albert (Box 46)
  - Hamilton, Charles W. (Box 46)
  - Hamilton, J.G. deRoulhac (Box 46)
  - Hamilton, John J. (Box 46)
  - Hamlin, Augustus C. (Box 46)
  - Hamlin, Charles E. (Box 46)
  - Hamlin, Edward (Box 46)
  - Hamlin, Hammibal E. (Box 46)
  - Hammond, Edward Spann (Box 46)
  - Hammond, Harry (Box 46)
  - Hammond, M.B. (Box 46)
  - Hannenfeldt, Mary (Box 46)
  - Harding, Madeline (Box 46)
  - Harper & Bros. Publishers (Box 46)
  - Harper & Bros.: The Editors (Box 46)
  - Harper, Frank (Box 46)
  - Harper, William R. (Box 46)
  - Harraca, Emile (Box 46)
  - Harraca, Emmanuel (Box 46)
  - Harris and Eving, Photographers (Box 46)
  - Harris, J.R. (Box 46)
  - Harris, Thomas L. (Box 46)
  - Harrison, Frederic (Box 46)
  - Harrison, Godfrey (Box 46)
  - Hart, Albert Bushnell (Box 46)
  - Hart, J.G. (Box 46)
  - Hartog, Alfred (Box 46)
  - Harvey, W.S. (Box 46)
  - Harvey, William S. (Box 46)
  - Haskell, Henry S. (Box 46)
  - Haskin, Frederic J. (Box 46)
  - Haskins, Charles H. (Box 46)
  - Hassels, John H. (Box 46)
  - Haultain, Arnold (Box 46)
  - Hawke, C.P. (Box 46)
  - Hawley, Joseph Roswell (Box 46)
  - Hay, Clara S. Mrs John) (Box 46)
  - Hayes, Birchard A. (Box 46)
  - Hayes, Henry W. (Box 46)
  - Hazen, Charles D. (Box 46)
  - Hazlitt, Henry (Box 46)
  - Healey, Frances (Box 46)
  - Healey, Richard J. (Box 47)
  - Healy, Margaret [Mrs. Edgar Bancroft] (Box 47)
  - Heckman, Wallace (Box 47)
  - Heckscher, Henrietta (Box 47)
  - Heitmuller, Anton (Box 47)
  - Helper, Hinton Reran (Box 47)
  - Hemphill, John J. (Box 47)
  - Henderson, A.T. (Box 47)
  - Henderson, E. Prioleau (Box 47)
  - Henderson, Ernest F. (Box 47)
  - Henderson, Estelle A. (Box 47)
  - Henderson, Gov. Charles (Box 47)
  - Henderson, John B. (Box 47)
  - Henderson, John B.. Jr. (Box 47)
  - Hendrick, Burton J. (Box 47)
  - Henry, H.M. (Box 47)
  - Henry, William Wirt (Box 47)
  - Herbert, Col. Hilary Abner (Box 47)
  - Hermann, Arthur L. (Box 47)
  - Hersen, J.C. (Box 47)
  - Hicks, Margaret de Forest (Box 47)
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth (Box 47)
  - Hill, Abby B. (Box 48)
  - Hill, Bessie (Box 48)
  - Hill, David J. (Box 48)
  - Hill, John L. (Box 48)
  - Hill, Juliet L.P. (Box 48)
  - Hill, Louise Allston (Box 48)
  - Hill, Paul A. (Box 48)
  - Hilles, Florence Bayard (Box 48)
  - Hirooka Family (Box 48)
  - Hirooka, Kame (Box 48)
  - Hirsch, Joseph (Box 48)
  - Hiscock, Frank (Box 48)
  - Hitchcock, Bradford W. (Box 48)
  - Hitchcock, Ripley (Box 48)
  - Hitt, R.R. (Box 48)
  - Hoar, George F. (Box 48)
  - Hoar, Miss Mary (Box 48)
  - Hobbs, J. Howard (Box 48)
  - Hodges, Herbert H. (Box 48)
  - Hoit, Alice M. (Box 48)
  - Holden, P.G. (Box 48)
  - Holland, J.W. (Box 48)
  - Holman, William S. (Box 48)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell (Box 48)
  - Holsey, Albon L. (Box 48)
  - Holt, W. Stull (Box 48)
  - Home, Helen S. (Box 48)
  - Hooper, F.H. (Box 48)
  - Hoover, Anna F. (Box 48)
  - Hopkins, Nevil Monroe (Box 48)
  - Horan, C. (Box 48)
  - Hornaday, William Temple (Box 48)
  - Hosner, G.W. (Box 48)
  - Houston, David Franklin (Box 48)
  - Howard, George (Box 48)
  - Howe, Archibald (Box 48)
  - Howe, Daniel Wait (Box 48)
  - Howe, M.A. DeWolfe (Box 48)
  - Howe, W.B. (Box 48)
  - Hoyt, Keplet (Box 48)
  - Hradil, Mary (Box 48)
  - Hudson, Oscar (Box 48)
  - Huidekoper, Reginald S. (Box 48)
  - Hulsmith, Elsie (Box 48)
  - Hunt, Gaillard (Box 48)
  - Hunt, James E. (Box 48)
  - Hurd, Henry M. (Box 48)
  - Imamura, Sakio (Box 49)
  - Imes, G. Lake (Box 49)
  - Ingle, Edward (Box 49)
  - International Harvester Co. (Box 49)
  - Iverson, Alfred (Box 49)
  - J.H. Fuest Company (Box 49)
  - Jackson, Cordelia (Box 49)
  - Jacobi, A. (Box 49)
  - Jameson, J. Franklin (Box 49)
  - Jameson, Sara Elwell (Box 49)
  - Jaray, Gabriel Louis (Box 49)
  - Jennings, Arthur H. (Box 49)
  - Jeralmon, Harry M. (Box 49)
  - Jerome, William Travers (Box 49)
  - Jervey, Theodore D. (Box 49)
  - Johnsen, Charles E. (Box 49)
  - Johnson, Allen (Box 49)
  - Johnson, G.E. (Box 49)
  - Johnson, John (Box 49)
  - Johnson, Mabel (Box 49)
  - Johnson, Nelson Trusler (Box 49)
  - Johnson, Paul E. (Box 49)
  - Johnson, R.U. (Box 49)
  - Johnson, Thomas Cary (Box 49)
  - Johnston, D.V.R. (Box 49)
  - Johnston, Frank (Box 49)
  - Johnston, Grace Douglas (Box 49)
  - Jones, Charles Edgeworth (Box 49)
  - Jones, Eugene Kinckle (Box 49)
  - Jones, George M. (Box 49)
  - Jones, James (Box 49)
  - Jones, Thomas D. (Box 49)
  - Jonhfield, J.M. (Box 49)
  - Jordan, J.L. (Box 49)
  - Judson, Harry Pratt (Box 49)
  - Julian, George W. (Box 49)
  - Justice, Queen (Box 49)
  - Kato, S. (Box 49)
  - Kauffmann, Louise (Box 49)
  - Kauffraan, Miriam (Box 49)
  - Kaupp, Josephine (Box 49)
  - Kawakami, K.K. (Box 49)
  - Kellner, Ernest (Box 49)
  - Kennan, George (Box 49)
  - Kennedy, John L. (Box 49)
  - Kent, Charles W. (Box 49)
  - Kent, Dorman E. Eaton (Box 49)
  - Kimball, John C. (Box 49)
  - Kimberley, Mandi L. (Box 49)
  - Kimberley, S.A. (Box 49)
  - Kindall, Elizabeth (Box 49)
  - King, Charles (Box 49)
  - King, Stanley (Box 49)
  - Kittredge, Edmund W. (Box 49)
  - Knapp, E.J. (Box 49)
  - Knoop, Claire (Box 49)
  - Knoop, E. (Box 49)
  - Komatsu, Takashi (Box 49)
  - Kppleton, William W. (Box 49)